尼克  我得跟你談談
Nick! We need to talk.
溫斯頓留下  沒什么好談的了
Winston stays. End of discussion.
不是
No, dude.
我收到了你的感恩節邀請
I got your Thanksgiving invitation.
感恩節盛會
-這是你做的嗎  -當然不是
- Did you make this? - Absolutely not.
他在宣布感恩節的到來
He's announcing Thanksgiving!
他拿著小號  宣布盛會召開
With his little trumpet, he's announcing the feast!
太好玩了
It's so funny...
我們給他起名叫羅格吧
We should name that little guy Roger.
你那蛋蛋掉出來的時候
When your testicles fell off,
是帶了多少雌性激素啊
did you form lady parts,
還是你太陰虛了
or is it kind of like a Gonzo nose down there?
-這是個好問題  -是吧
- It's really interesting. - Yeah.
但是吧
You see, the thing is,
-我的蛋蛋其實還沒下來呢  -是哦
- my testicles haven't fallen off... -Right.
還早著呢
...it's just the morning.
還有外面很冷的時候
And my testicles do this really unique thing
我的蛋蛋會很有特點地蜷縮
of burrowing... when it's cold out.
你就是在氣我吧
You're burning me.
-我得跟你說句實話  -洗耳恭聽
- I gotta be real with you. - Please.
我知道男人一般
I know how a guy can get, like,
在感情中總會迷失
lost in a relationship.
我感同身受
I've been there, dude. You're snuggling,
你就在那纏綿啊  纏綿啊  纏綿啊
you're snuggling, you're snuggling,
突然之間你就變了
and then, bam!
之后你就會
Next thing you know, you're wearing
開始穿迷你裙  抹胸裝
a jean skirt and a tube top with no panties on,
因為你們會說好
because you guys said you were gonna
在萬圣節打扮成對方的模樣
dress up like each other for Halloween.
但她卻不會穿成你的樣子
But she doesn't dress up like you.
但你們還是會去萬圣節派對
But you still go to the party.
那我實在是太遺憾了
I could not be more sorry for you,
因為我們不是這樣的
but that's not my story.
那你站起來
Stand up.
-站起來  -對
- Stand up?  - Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
你穿的是杰茜卡的睡褲嗎
Are those Jessica's pajama bottoms?
這是運動服
It's, uh... football player pants for, uh,
關注乳腺癌活動的運動服
br-breast cancer awareness.
我喜歡它對我小巨蛋的包裹感
I like the way that they hug my gronk.
杰茜駕到  第三季第十集
感恩節去野營么
Camping on Thanksgiving?
可能是個瘋狂的尼克式想法  但我還挺喜歡的
It might be a crazy Nick idea, but I kind of like it.
我還以為你討厭野營和大自然呢
I thought you hated camping and nature.
你不是說你害怕蒼蠅
You said you were afraid a fly was gonna
會飛進你的腦袋洞悉你的想法嗎
fly in your head and learn all your thoughts.
我是個爺們  爺們就要有野性
I am a man, and men belong in wilderness.
這對我很重要
It really means a lot to me.
我在乎的只有
The only thing I care about
我們能待在一會兒
is that we're all together.
我們能坐在一起
And that we can all sit down together
吃頓晚餐就挺好了
and have a nice dinner.
我完全同意
I 100% agree.
我覺得大家會喜歡這個主意的
I think everybody's gonna love this idea.
我也覺得
Me, too.
-野營  瘋了吧  -我們又不是動物
- Camping? What the hell? - Like we're animals?
聽他說嘛
Come on. Hear him out.
想想吧
Let's face it.
我們在家度過的感恩節可都不怎么樣
Our indoor Thanksgivings haven't been so great.
-火雞  -有死人
- Turkey! - Dead body!
我覺得我喜歡上你媽了
I think I'm into your mother.
這次不可能更糟了
So this can't be worse.
謝謝你杰茜卡  我接著說
Thank you, Jessica, I got it from here.
-不客氣  -今年感恩節
- All right. - This Thanksgiving,
我要發揚我們祖先的傳統
I want to honor the traditions of our forefathers.
當年清教徒和土著人相處融洽
The mighty Pilgrims and Native Americans
才得以共同生存
who came together in order to survive.
是啊
Sure, yeah.
在合作的歷史上展開了新的篇章
The first chapter in a proud history of cooperation.
野營將是對我們的男子氣概
It'll be the ultimate test of manhood
和生存能力的終極考驗
and our survival skills.
-是嗎  -怎么考驗男子氣概
- It will? - How's this for a test of our manhood?
我們呆在家
We stay at home,
喝酒  看球
we drink beer, we watch football.
-那才是男人  -我喜歡
- Manhood. - I like that idea.
溫斯頓  我在說純爺們兒該做的事
Winston, I'm talking about real men.
-我說的也是啊  -能夠自我打拼的純爺們兒
- Me, too. - Men who fend for themselves.
你是我認識的最懶的人了
You're the laziest man I know.
杰茜  你說實話
Okay, Jess, be honest with me.
你們滾床單的時候他在上面過嗎
Has he ever been on top?
純爺們兒都在下面
Real men are on the bottom.
才不是
No, they're not.
-你在下面吧  -大家聽我說
- You're on the bottom... - Guys, guys.
這可是感恩節
It's Thanksgiving.
我們得在一起過
We need to be together.
誰想去野營
Who's in?
舉手啊  親們
Come on, guys!
-好吧  我去  -什么
- All right, I'm in. - What?
-施密特  太棒了  -太棒了
- Yeah, Schmidt! - Yes!
以前我爸媽一直都在鬧離婚
Look, my parents were super divorced
根本就沒帶我去野營過
and they never took me camping,
但我覺得我應該還挺擅長這個的
but I always thought that I'd be incredible at it.
快去準備吧
Let's get ready.
施密特  你頭上戴的這是啥啊
What the hell is on your head, Schmidt?
簡直就是山寨維戈·莫特森
It's an exact replica of the hat
在《殺魔騎兵》里戴的帽子
Viggo Mortensen wore in Hidalgo.
我就知道你會喜歡
Knew you'd like it.
天啊
Wow!
太棒了  米勒
Nice job, Miller!
這里太美了
This spot's beautiful.
是吧
I know.
-希希  -希希也來了
- Cece! - Cece's here?
我不知道她會來
I didn't know she was gonna be here.
真高興你來了
Yay, I'm so happy you came!
大家都團聚在一起了
We're all together!
-我太激動了  -當然了
- It makes me so excited. - Of course!
還有什么比和我的前男友
I mean, what could be better
以及剛和我約過會的前男友的朋友
than camping in the woods with my ex-boyfriend
一起去森林里野營更好的事呢
and his friend I just made out with.
你剛和誰約會了
With whom you just made out.
別說了  你知道我不喜歡這樣
Don't. You know I hate that.
-別問了  -語法是很重要的
- Don't. - Grammar's important.
說真的  別問了
Seriously, don't.
如果你們相處不來  我會來救你的
If it get awkward, I'll come save you.
感恩節快樂
Happy Thanksgiving!
你好嗎  小妞
Hey, what's up, girl?
好啊  希希
Hey, Cece.
我從沒...
Hey, I never, uh...
問過你
had a chance to ask you.
你們...
How did the, um...
你們那天晚上約會得如何
How'd your guys' date go the other night?
-和希希一起那次嗎  -是的
- Oh, with Cece? - Yeah.
那...我覺得很棒
Uh... it was... I loved it.
我是說  很不錯
I mean, it was good.
-很不錯  -那很好啊
- It was cool. - That's great.
-超級  -超級爽
- Super. - Super-duper.
那你覺得在哪里搭帳篷比較好
So where you thinking about pitching, uh, pitching a tent?
我覺得那兒比較好
Thinking over there.
那邊嗎  當然了
Oh, yonder? Sure.
-那邊  -聽著  在過去的12小時
- Yonder. - Listen, I've been researching on the Internet
我一直在網上搜索
for the past 12 hours
關于森林需要知道的一切
everything there is to know about the wood.
現在  我是個露營高手了
Now I'm a... I'm a master camper.
如果你需要幫忙的話
So if you need any help with anything,
只管來問我  好嗎
just come to me and ask, okay?
謝你了  兄弟
Thanks, man.
關于森林什么的我一無所知
I don't know anything about the wood.
-我什么都知道  -我簡直是云里霧里
- I know everything. - I'm lost.
那是什么  樹嗎
What is that, a tree?
如果把這些樹換成高樓大廈
If these trees were skyscrapers,
-你就舒服多了吧  -是啊
- you'd feel very comfortable. - Yeah.
那就像在家里一樣舒服  不幸的是
I'd be right at home. Unfortunately,
它們就是樹
they're actual trees.
-你最棒了  -我喜歡你的帽子
- You're the best. - I love the hat!
抱歉  那是太陽能手機充電器嗎
I'm sorry, is that a solar cell phone charger?
是啊  沒有它的話我撐不過兩天
Yeah, I can't go more than two days without it.
等等  你也...討厭野營嗎
Okay, hold on. Do you... do you hate camping, too?
你在開玩笑嗎  我恨死野營了
Are you kidding me? I absolutely hate camping.
那我們還待在這里干嘛
Then why are we here?
因為我沒有話語權  我從來沒有過
Because I didn't get a say. I never get a say.
不管我想做什么  他們鳥都不鳥我
Whenever I want to do something, they don't give a hoot.
猜猜看誰拿到了去陶瓷研討會的入場券
Guess who just got free passes to a pottery seminar.
-快出去吧  -溫斯頓
- Get out of here. - Winston!
我們本來可以做最棒的馬克杯的
We could've made the craziest mugs, man.
-尼克  -在
- Hey, Nick? - Yeah.
這里只有啤酒
There's just beer in here.
這應該能夠我們喝上幾個小時的
That should last us for the first few hours, actually.
食物在哪兒
Where's the food?
那些我做的派在哪兒
Where... where are all the pies I made?
別擔心  杰茜
Look, don't worry, Jess.
因為食物就在...就在這里
'Cause the food is... right here.
抱歉  我不太懂那個手勢是什么意思
I'm... sorry. I don't understand that gesture.
我們要出去打獵覓食
We're gonna be hunting and foraging for our dinner,
就像印第安人和清教徒那樣
just like the Indians and the Pilgrims.
但你帶了啤酒來
But you brought beer.
你沒法覓到啤酒的  這是必需品
You can't forage for beer. And that's a necessity.
這就是感恩節晚餐嗎
So this is Thanksgiving meal?
96罐熱啤酒
96 warm beers?
我們可以這樣
We can do this.
伙計們  我們變得很軟弱
Guys, we've gotten soft!
就因為抗生素和止疼膏
With our antibiotics and our sports creams.
你們覺得喬治·華盛頓會養寵物貓嗎
Do you think George Washington had a pet cat?
-是啊  -不  他不會
- Yeah. - No. He didn't.
-他捕獵貓  -你說啥
- He hunted them. - What?
他從它們身上榨取了奶和黃油
And he made milk and butter out of their spoils.
這太可怕了
That's terrible.
你是說喬治·華盛頓給他的貓擠奶嗎
So you're saying George Washington milked his cat?
-聽起來太不正常了  -完全沒有
- Nothing is sounding accurate right now. - Not at all.
你從哪兒讀到這個的
Where'd you read this?
我沒說這很簡單
I'm not saying it's gonna be easy.
這很困難
It's gonna be hard.
但我們一定能完成的
But we will emerge out of this
我們會成為更好的朋友  成為一個部落
better friends and a tribe.
我參加
I'm on board.
返璞歸真嘛
Going old-school.
上啊  殺啊  捕獵啊  上啊
Men! Killing! Hunting! Men!
上啊  上啊  上啊  上啊
Men! Men! Men! Men!
我的牛仔帽  我的牛仔...
Oh, my cowman's... my cowman...
我的牛仔帽  我的牛仔帽
my cowman's hat, my cowman's hat.
伙計們  聽我說
Guys, look,
我和這里的所有人一樣有血性
I'm as much a man as anybody here,
但這個計劃簡直是太挫了
but this plan is straight-up dookie.
我需要糖果  我需要游行
I need my sweets and I need my parade.
你知道嗎  我也不參加了
Yeah, you know what? I'm out, too.
同志們  同志們  聽我說
Guys, guys, guys. Look.
我們團圓了
We're together.
我們是一家人
We're a family.
這是感恩節啊
It's Thanksgiving.
我保證尼克是計劃好了的  對吧
And I'm sure Nick has a plan. Right?
-我當然有計劃了  -太好了
- Oh, yeah. I've got a plan. - Great.
-你有計劃  -那個人有計劃
- You got a plan? - The man's got a plan.
這些野外指南詳細的介紹了
These wilderness guides right here detail what plants
什么植物能吃  什么陷阱能造
are safe for eating and what traps we can build.
不幸的是  我沒錢了
Unfortunately, I ran out of money,
所以我沒法打印
so I couldn't print out the chapters
開膛破肚和剝皮的內容  不過
on gutting and skinning, but...
等我們到了那一步再說吧
we'll worry about that when we get there.
按清教徒的規矩
Pilgrim rules.
男人打獵
Men, hunters!
女人搜集食材
Women, foragers.
我才不打獵  要打我也只打
I'm not hunting. The only hunt I want
邦妮或者海倫
is Bonnie or Helen.
Bonnie Hunt和Helen Hunt是兩個女明星
雖然都姓Hunt  但沒有親戚關系
你懂的  教練
You know what I'm talking about, Coach.
不懂
What?
尼克
Nick.
太完美了  回歸自然的原始人
This is perfect. Primal man in nature.
圍捕獵物  現在誰才像個娘們  教練
Stalking prey. Who's basically the lady now, Coach?
這二十分鐘我都見到這棵樹六次了
I've seen that tree six times in the past 20 minutes.
我們肯定在兜圈子
We're definitely moving in a small circle.
那我就這樣  我往這邊開出一條小路
Here's what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna clear a path this way.
我們一路向北
We will travel northbound, I believe.
那不是北邊  是南邊
That's not north, that's south.
南邊嗎  那我們就一路向南
That is south? Then let's travel southbound.
我來開路  要是里面有什么
I'm gonna clear a path. If something's in there
而你被它傷到的話  我會幫你快速了斷的
and you get injured, I promise you I will kill you fast.
糞便  糞便
Scat! Scat.
-這附近有只動物  -施密特  那是顆葡萄干
- There's an animal nearby. - Hey, Schmidt, that's a raisin, man.
這不是葡萄干  這就是動物糞便
That's not a raisin. This is scat.
好吧
Okay.
這肯定是糞便
That's poop for sure.
我是對的  打臉哦  尼克
I was right. In your face, Nick.
-打臉哦  尼克  -所以呢
- In your face, Nick. - How so?
不知道  他把  把一顆糞便吃了
I don't know, he put a... put a turd in his mouth.
-所以那就打我臉了  真是  -沒錯
- And that's in my face? So that's... - Yeah.
我覺得我們還沒到吃屎的地步  施密特
I don't think we should start eating poo yet, Schmidt.
盡管等著吧
Let's wait on that.
你要不要吃點土清清口
You want to chase that with some dirt?
有人有口香糖嗎
Does anyone have any gum?
沒有
No.
我一開始就不想這樣的
Not that I wanted any in the first place.
那洞也太大了  尼克
That's a mighty big hole there, Nick.
你想逮個大冰箱么
You trying to catch a refrigerator?
這是個熊洞
It's a bear hole.
熊掉進去  然后其他東西掉進去
Bear falls in, other stuff falls in.
我們就拿熊不要的
We take what the bear doesn't want.
-有道理  -經典的人熊團隊
- Makes sense. - Classic human/bear team-up.
我是芝加哥人  我只能做到這樣了
I'm from Chicago. It's the best I can do.
是啊  熊都喜歡跟你分享食物
Yeah, bears love to share.
等那只熊掉進洞里的時候
What are you planning on doing with
你打算怎么做
that bear when he falls into the hole?
伙計  我已經盡力了
Dude, I'm trying the best that I can!
我們沒有吃的
We have no food.
我來告訴你吧  尼克
Let me explain something to you, Nick.
在做陷阱的時候
When you're building a trap,
得為你的獵物一一量身定制
you want to customize it to your prey.
所以呢  如果我想抓
So, I don't know, if I was
比如說  松鼠的話
trying to catch, say a squirrel,
我會像松鼠一樣思考
I'd want to think like a squirrel.
容我用我造的這個陷阱來做演示
Allow me to demonstrate with this trap that I built.
你怎么能像松鼠一樣思考呢
How do you get into the mindset of a squirrel?
我是只松鼠  對吧
I'm a squirrel... right?
-學得真像  -看這里
- You do that really well. - Look at this!
這兒有些堅果
Oh, there's some nuts here.
看這些可愛的小堅果
Look at all these little nuts.
你最好別那么做
You might not want to do that.
我要是想學紡紗的話
If I needed your advice on how to lead a spinning class,
我會請教你的  但這可是我的專業領域
I'd ask you, but this is my territory.
-我的肩胛骨  -兄弟  你沒事吧
- My scapula! - Dude, are you all right?
快弄開
Aah! Aah, get it off! Aah!
快
Get it!
起來  深呼吸
Get up. Keep breathing, man.
我不是故意要笑的
I don't mean to be laughing,
-你還好嗎  -我得給你綁個繃帶
- but are you okay? - I’m gonna make you a sling.
你要干嘛
You're gonna make me a what?
-你根本不會  -繃帶
- You don't know how to do that. - A sling.
我當然會綁
Of course I do.
你在干嘛
What...?What are you doing?
我當年可是鷹級童子軍[最高級童子軍]
I was an Eagle Scout.
你在說什么呢  你是鷹級童子軍
What are you talking about, you were an Eagle Scout?
-你看吧  -確實還不錯
- Look. - That's actually really good.
很抱歉  伙計  你想做野營第一人
I'm sorry, dude. You wanted to be the best at camping.
你又對你那頂帽子那么興奮
You were so excited about your hat.
我并不想干預
I didn't want to get in the way of that.
再加上整個關于希希的事
Plus with the whole Cece thing or whatever.
你說什么呢
What are you talking about?
我的第一是你讓出來的嗎
You're gonna let me be the best camper.
-我就是野營第一人  -是啊
- I am the best camper! - Yeah.
我覺得這是菊苣
I think this is chicory.
書上說它的根可以吃
It says you can eat the root.
這也可能是茉莉
Or it's jasmine.
吃了會死的
Which will kill you.
你們怎么看
Hmm. What do you guys think?
-肯定沒事的  -盡管吃吧
- I’m sure it's fine. - Yeah, just eat it.
樹莓
Hey, raspberries!
這兒
There... Ow!
這兒有很多樹莓
There are a lot of brambles in here.
離這兒不遠有家鄉村小店
There's a country store not far from here.
三星半  評論說
Three and a half stars. The reviews say,
"湊活能吃不過很臟"
"It's functional and dusty."
我覺得還行
Sounds good to me.
棒極了  誰來幫幫我
This is so fun. Who wants to help?
這計劃顯然是最糟糕的
This plan is officially the worst.
我們要餓死了
We are starving.
盡管承認吧  你也不想這么做
Just admit, you don't want to do this, either.
聽好了
Okay, listen up.
只能買森林里能找到的東西  好嗎
Only stuff we can find in the forest, right?
看那魚
Look at that fish.
棒極了
It's perfect.
-不是吧  -我得把它抓來
- What? Oh, - I’m gonna grab it.
餓死了  終于要開餐了  弟兄們
I'm so hungry. Now we get to eat, boys.
哥們  那看起來像是死的
Dude, that looks dead.
伙計們  積極一點兒
Guys, stop being negative right now.
一面翻上來表示它已經死了
Laying on its side means it's dead.
我才不想進到水里呢  哥們
I wouldn't get in that water, man.
你會得賈第蟲病的
You're gonna get beaver fever.
現在誰是孬種啊  教練
Where are my testicles now, Coach?
等他逮到那個小可憐時
When he catches that little critter,
我會給你表演怎么給它刮鱗
I'm gonna show you how to scale it.
疼嗎
That hurts?
當然疼了
Yeah, it hurts!
一塊石頭掉在了我的...
A boulder fell on my...
你這么做是因為我取笑你的邀請嗎
Is all this 'cause I teased you about the invite?
是的  義無反顧
Yes, it is! No regrets!
拜托  尼克
Aw! Aw, come on, Nick.
-成功了  -別鬧了
- Yes! - Quit it.
你們可能是對的  它可能是死的
You guys might be right! It might be dead!
事實上  確實是死魚
In fact, it was dead!
聞著還挺...新鮮
Smells fresh... enough!
拜托  溫斯頓
Oh, come on, Winston, what?
你剛做完指甲還是怎么著  把蘋果弄臟
You just get your nails done? Get the apple dirty!
蹭點兒灰塵上去
Grind some dirt in it, grind some dirt in it.
-我的神啊  好餓  -嗨
- God, I'm so hungry! - Hey, hey!
看男人們帶回來了什么
Hey. Look what the men brought.
-哎呦  不錯呦  -計劃湊效了
- Oh, hey! Hey, hey! - The plan worked.
他看起來像個斗士
Hey, he looks like a fighter.
他確實算是  某種程度上說
He really was, kind of.
-神啊  -哇
- Oh, my God! - Wow.
-不算什么啦  -哇
- I mean, well... - Whoa.
-像自助餐一樣  -你們干得很好
- Like a smorgasbord. - You guys did great.
-是啊  -對
- Yeah, we did. - Yep.
你們從哪弄的腰果
Where'd you get the cashews?
-灌木叢上  -對
- Um, on a bush. - Yeah.
甜菜呢
How about the beets?
-也是灌木上的  -沒錯
- Also a bush. - That's right.
好吧
Yeah.
那牛油果呢
The avocado?
-還是灌木上  -是的
- Also on a bush. - That's right.
看看我們  離家遠行
Well, look at us. Living off the land,
自力更生
fending for ourselves.
我們有魚還有水果
We got fish and fruits,
還有這個可能是我這輩子
and this is probably gonna be the most delicious apple
吃過的最好吃的蘋果
I've ever eaten in my life.
為什么是俄勒岡州生產
"Product of Oregon"?
我們剛才居然走到俄勒岡州了
We walked to Oregon?
-啥  -怎么可能
- What? - What?
-難怪抽筋呢  -是啊  -這地方...
- That's why this cramp... - Yeah... - This place...
拜托  你們真以為我們三個是笨蛋嗎
Come on, you think the three of us are true dumb-asses?
我們不是  從開始我就差不多知道了
We're not. I kind of knew from the beginning.
你們不可能做到的
I mean, there's no way.
這些都是你們從商店買的吧
You just went to a store and got all this?
我覺得是
I think so.
我覺得這些都是他們買來的
I think they definitely bought everything from the store.
我想要的就是
The one thing I wanted
大家一起坐下來吃頓晚飯
was for us all to sit down together and have dinner,
沒有東西吃怎么行
and you can't do that without dinner.
我們有東西吃
We have dinner.
那魚看起來有點像河馬肉
That fish kind of looks like hippo meat.
哥們  別這樣
Come on, man.
讓我們坐下來
Let's just sit down
品嘗美味的扁桃仁吧
and eat some delicious almonds.
-好好享受  -是啊
- And enjoy ourselves. - Yes.
一起好好過一個感恩節
And have a really nice Thanksgiving together.
拜托了  尼克  開吃吧
Come on, Nick, let's eat.
別鬧了  哥們  開吃吧
Come on, man, let's eat.
我有種第一個感恩節時人們的感覺
I feel like how they must've felt on the first Thanksgiving.
被背叛了
Betrayed.
-尼克  -啥
- Nick - What?
你們過你們的吧
Happy Thanksgiving.
-拜托  尼克  -別這樣
- Oh, come on. Nick, come on! - Don't do this.
得告訴你一下  首個感恩節挺和諧的
FYI, the first Thanksgiving was the good one.
別鬧了  尼克
Come on, Nick!
這些牛油果很貴的
These avocados were expensive!
開吃
Here we go.
好香啊
It smells so good.
我都等不及了
I can't wait till it's ready.
會撐死我的
I'm gonna be so stuffed.
魚眼睛掉了
The eyeball fell off.
你就知道它有多鮮美了
That's how you know it's good.
當烤好的時候它們就會掉出來
They got to pop out when it's ready, I think.
現在終于可以攤牌了
Now that the cards are finally on the table,
我們知道誰才是真正的露營大師了
I guess we can see who the true camp master really is.
-答案就是我  -誰先生好火誰就贏
- The answer's me. - First one to make a flame wins.
開動吧
Let's do this.
看好了
Now, check this out.
哥教你怎么生火
This is how you make a flame.
你那兩塊石頭  這么互相敲
You go with two rocks. One against the other.
產生摩擦
You create friction.
-搞定了  -啥
- I'm done. - What?
-搞定了  -那算不上火苗  快滅了都
- I'm done. - Well, that's barely a flame, it's going out.
我的個親娘啊  你是誰  巫師嗎
Whoa! Well, goodness gracious! What are you? A sorcerer?
媽的
Damn it!
山頂洞人
Hey, mountain man.
你想過來和我們一起吃些臟的蔬菜嗎
You want to come eat some dirty vegetables with us?
我應該猜到那甜菜不是野生的
I should've known those beets weren't from nature.
野生的長不出紫色
Nothing purple grows in nature.
聽著  我們沒有挺過來  好吧
Look, we didn't come through, okay?
你堅持下來了
You came through!
你都抓了條魚
Look, you caught a fish!
真了不起
That's really, really impressive.
你怎么做到的
How'd you do it?
空手抓的
With my bare hands.
-不是吧  你太強了  -是啊
- No way! You're so strong. - Yeah.
當時是...我和它搏斗來著...
Yeah, it was... It fought...
你想干嘛
What are you doing?
我沒想干嘛  我覺得太了不起了
I'm not doing anything. I think that's amazing.
你為我們帶來食物
You provided for us.
-你是男人  -別恭維我  杰茜
- You're a man. - Don't patronize me, Jess.
-沒有啊  -自從我們開始交往  杰茜
- I'm not. - Ever since we started dating, Jess,
做了好多女孩才做的事
we've been doing a bunch of girly stuff,
有些我挺喜歡  而且我喜歡你  但是
and I like some of it and you, but...
我的酒量已經...
My tolerance to alcohol has, like,
低得嚇人了
gotten really, scary low.
喝三罐啤酒
I drank three beers, and I got,
我就笑嘻嘻的  還犯困
like, all giggly and tired.
不想再喝了
And I didn't want a fourth.
昨晚我做了個夢  夢見刷洗一匹馬
Last night, I had a dream that I was brushing a horse.
感覺我有點找不到自我了
I just feel like I'm losing myself a little.
你就...
Just...
讓我吃了這條惡心的魚吧
Let me eat this disgusting fish and...
-不  尼克  尼克  -讓我死這兒得了
- No, Nick, Nick. - Yeah, just let me be over here.
這是我見過的最漂亮的魚
This is the most beautiful fish I've ever seen.
-別碰  我就不碰它  -真的很漂亮
- Don't touch... I wouldn't touch it. - It is! It is.
杰茜  不要  別把手伸進...
Jess, don't... Don't put your hands in...
我的天...
Oh, my lo...
吐出來
Spit it out.
芳香滿口
Fragrant.
我能嘗到湖水的滋味
Mmm, I can really... I can really taste the lake.
-吐出來  -我覺得自己在湖里與魚嬉戲
- Spit it out. - I feel like I'm there in the lake with the fish.
有刺
Bony.
咽下去的時候有點疼
That's gonna hurt going down.
但是我喜歡
But I like it.
痛得好開心  痛得好開心
Hurts so good! Hurts so good!
杰茜  我抓到這條魚的時候它已經死了
Jess, that fish was dead when I caught it.
還有只襪子浮在旁邊
There was a sock near it.
-我陪著你  -不要
- I'm gonna come with you. - No.
杰茜  讓我陪你吧
Jess, let me come with you.
-你去哪  -這邊有東西
- Where are you going? - There's something over here.
-我去看看  -杰茜
- I'm gonna look at it. - Jess...
我看到了一些有意思的東西
I'm seeing some interesting things.
我星期五之前都不在辦公室
I'm out of the office till Friday.
需要緊急援助
For immediate assistance,
請致電Deb軟件的推廣交流負責人斯萊特
please call Deb at extension A.C. Slater.
你們看到她往哪走了嗎
You guys see where she went?
-沒有  -沒看到  杰茜
- No. - No. Jess?
-杰茜  -杰茜
- Jess? - Jess?
杰茜
Jess!
杰茜  杰茜
Jess? Jess?
杰茜
Jess?
Jess!
做決定之前
I just want to see more carpet samples
我想多看看地毯樣品
before I make a final decision.
杰茜
Jess!
Jess?
杰茜  杰茜  你在哪
Jess! Jess, where are you?
-杰茜  -杰茜卡
- Jess! - Jessica!
天啊  都是我的錯
Oh, God, this is all my fault.
你知道嗎教練  我很喜歡那封請柬
You know what coach, I did like the invitation.
是我做的  我喜歡那個小號手
I made it. And I liked the little trumpet guy.
我覺得他很可愛
I thought he was cute.
- 這創意好得不得了  -什么
It's genius as a damn button! - What?
這么多石頭
So many stone...
伙計們快看  她在哪
Hey, guys, look. There she is!
這有好多狗印著美元的符號
There are dogs that have dollar signs
但卻沒有自己的銀行
but don't even own banks.
杰茜  我們在這  杰茜
Jess, we're over here! Jess!
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
那棵樹好像以前在哪見過  杰茜  停下
I've seen that tree before. Jess, stop!
捕熊的陷阱
The bear trap!
-不要  -我來了
- No! - I'm coming!
杰茜
Jess!
頭先著地  為什么
Headfirst? Why?
他大爺...
Son of a...
天啊  杰茜  真抱歉
Oh, my God, Jess, I am so sorry.
我是笨蛋
I was an idiot.
這個感恩節計劃太蠢了
This Thanksgiving plan was so stupid.
你不該吃那條魚  太對不起了
You shouldn't have eaten that fish. I'm sorry.
別讓他們付賬單  好嗎
Don't let them pay the bill, okay?
把支票給我
You bring the check to me.
不吵架了  月亮人
No arguments, moon man.
我的天
Oh, my God!
有人受傷嗎
Is anyone hurt?
我們沒事  我可能有幾根肋骨骨裂了
We're fine. I may have cracked a few ribs,
杰茜神經錯亂了
and, uh, Jess is delirious.
我猜她以為自己是兔子
I think she thinks she's a rabbit.
伙計們  我們會想辦法  好嗎
Guys, we're gonna figure something out, all right?
給我們扔條繩子或者棍子  其他什么也行
Just get us a rope or a stick or something.
-好吧  伙計有什么主意  -你在說什么
- All right, man, so, any ideas? - What are you talk...?
你自己知道  教練  別跟我打哈哈
You know what, Coach? Don't humor me.
-什么啊  -你知道該做什么
- What? - You know what to do.
聽著  我承認  你露營的本事比我好
Look, I admit it. You're a better camper than I am.
你的人生也比我好
You're better at life than I am.
沒準跟希希約會也比我好
You're probably better at dating Cece than I am.
那天晚上我看到你們了
I saw you guys the other night
在家門口卿卿我我
inhaling each other in front of the loft.
施密特  我們就干了那么點兒事  就沒了
Schmidt, that's all we did. That was it.
我問她要不要上樓  她說不要  好嗎
I asked her to come upstairs, she said no, okay?
現在她都不回我短信了
And now she won't return any of my text messages.
整個旅行她都無視我
She's been ignoring me this whole trip.
我一直是"你好哇"  她卻"嗯"
I'm all, like, "Hey." She's like, "Mm-hmm."
我就想"什么情況"
I'm like, "What?"
-你笑什么  伙計  -我沒笑
- Why are you smiling, dude? - I'm not smiling.
我在這跟你交心呢伙計
I'm over here baring my soul to you, dude,
而你卻當著我的面鬼笑
and you're freaking smiling in my face. Yeah.
我傾聽的時候都是這種表情
This is the face I make when I listen.
-你傾聽的時候所有牙都呲出來嗎  -沒有
-All your teeth show when you listen? - I'm not.
你還在笑  我跟你坦誠相待
You're smiling right now. I opened up to you.
-你卻惹我生氣  別笑了  -我沒笑
- You're pissing me off. Stop smiling. - I'm not.
我弄死你  你個瘋子
I will wreck you. You're crazy, man.
-你神經病  -住手  聽我說
- You're nuts. - Stop it, listen to me.
我們必須馬上解決這事
We are going to solve this right now.
好嗎  把褲子脫了
All right, take your pants off.
好吧  我不是什么鷹級童子軍
Okay, I am no Eagle Scout,
但我會把褲子綁成繩子
but I know how to make a pants rope.
-褲繩  -你真天才
- Pants rope. - You're a genius.
我知道  -好?
I know. - Okay.
你也脫褲子嗎
Are you gonna take off your pants?
是的  等我脫掉我的
Yeah, right after I take off
胸罩之后我們就可以把繩子扔到樹上了
my bra so we can anchor the rope to the tree.
-真的會發生嗎  -快點脫掉吧
- That's gonna happen for real? - Just take them off now.
看看溫斯頓的內褲
Whoa, look at Winston's pants.
上面還有小貓
It's got kittens on it.
不是貓
These aren't kittens.
我不敢相信我竟然是自愿來這里的
I cannot believe I'm here voluntarily.
-太傻了  -脫掉
- So stupid. - Take them off.
脫掉咯
They're coming off.
你們兩個  抓住繩子
Here, you guys, grab hold of the rope.
好了  你先請  杰茜
Okay, you go first, Jess.
我跟在你后面支援你
I'll be right behind you to support you.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
這樣吧  我背著你  咱倆一起上去
Okay, how about this? Get on my back, I'll bring us both up.
上來了
Back at you.
你能做到
You can do it!
給你  拿著手電筒
There, hold this flashlight, buddy.
抓住
Grab hold.
快  尼克  加油  加油
Come on, Nick! Come on. Here we go!
上帝  我要把你弄出去
Oh, God, I'm gonna get you out of here.
你的腿也用上  尼克
Use your legs, Nick.
加油  尼克
Come on, Nick!
加油
Come on.
溫斯頓  我討厭你的打底褲  加油
Ah, Winston, I hate your leggings. Come on.
快到了
Almost there.
-加油  -上來了
- Let's go. - You got it,
成功了
you got it.
You got it, you...
你個大胖混蛋
You chubby son of a bitch.
罵得好
Yeah.
你還好嗎  杰茜  沒事吧
You okay, Jess, you all right?
希爾貝利急救中心
謝謝你救了我  山頂洞人
Thanks for saving me, mountain man.
我有條來自醫生的好消息
So I've got good news from the doctor
你沒得狂犬病
you don't have rabies.
你身上有賈第鞭毛蟲
You have, uh, giardia
和一種叫軍團病的疾病
and something called Legionnaires' disease.
我很高興他們能保住你的腳
I'm just glad they were able to save your foot.
什么
What?
沒  沒什么
No, nothing.
別在意
Never mind.
我很抱歉整個野營的事
Hey, I'm sorry about the whole camping thing.
不  沒事的
Oh, no, it's okay.
我真傻
Ah, I was really stupid.
我不像我自己了
I haven't been myself.
你是我想要的男人
You're the man I want.
你想要的只是讓大家
All you wanted was for everyone
在感恩節能一起過  杰茜
to be together on Thanksgiving, Jess.
明年吧
Next year.
-薯片  -薯片
- Potato chips. - Chips?
你請客
Maybe a treat.
聽著  教練  本著感恩節的精神
Listen, Coach, uh, in the spirit of Thanksgiving,
我想也許我可以給你
I thought maybe that I could give you
有關希希的一些建議
some advice about... about Cece.
你認為我有多絕望
How desperate do you think I am?
我認為你或許非常絕望
I think you're probably very desperate.
我非常絕望  我的意思是
I'm very desperate, I mean,
她什么像樣的回應都沒有
she's giving me nothing.
對她說她很漂亮  她說謝謝
Told her she looked pretty, she said thanks.
那算哪門子心理戰
Mm-hmm. What kind of mind game is that?
教練  任何事對你而言都輕而易舉
Look, Coach, things have always come easy to you.
但希希不會成為那些事之一
Cece is not going to be one of those things.
我有一次曾經在一輛車窗上砸了
I once spent hours in a car
一個透氣孔的車里待了好幾個小時
with just a cracked window for air.
她進了一家俱樂部
She was going into a club
把我一個人扔在外面
and she just kind of left me there.
你為什么要笑
Why are you smiling about that?
伙計們  我想到一個挽救感恩節的辦法
Hey, guys, I figured out a way to save Thanksgiving.
-我有個計劃  -我受夠計劃了
- I got a plan. - Enough with the plans.
-你安排計劃的能力糟透了  -否決尼克·米勒的計劃
- You suck at plans! - Not another Nick Miller plan.
我愛你  但是你的計劃真的超爛
I love you, man, but you are terrible at plans.
現在才11點48分  感恩節快樂
It's still 11:48, so happy Thanksgiving.
什么
What?
我們有巴西堅果
Got us some Brazilian nuts,
幾個字母奶酪  還有點心
a couple of string cheeses, and snack.
謝謝
Thank you.
我手機上可以看感恩節游行
I got the parade on my phone.
太棒了
Yes.
做了一些裝飾
Made some decorations.
我想這個也許是火雞三明治
I think this may be a turkey sandwich,
不過我不確定
but I'm not sure,
我也知道這一切并不是
and I know this whole thing isn't...
很完美
It's perfect.
大家  你們開動吧別管我
Look, guys, start without me
因為我估計得過幾個星期才能吃東西了
because it might be a few weeks before I can eat again.
你吐了很多東西出來
You were throwing up a lot.
那太可怕了  真的
That was scary... seriously.
-我餓了  我們開吃吧  -開吃
- Okay, I'm starving actually. Let's eat. - Yeah, let's eat.
尼克在森林里找到的這些吃的
Nick found all this food in the woods.
我能喝姜汁汽水嗎
Can I have the ginger ale?
沒問題  尼克找到的  已經開了
Yeah, Nick found that. It's already open.
翻譯：Provindence 兮之 持久
翻譯：麥田守望者 CS小明漫畫家 MythCreator
時間軸：小式 Ans Chance-coco   后期：MythCreator
校對：衛老哥 丟丟曳  總監:  丟丟曳